<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Eddie Tu&#39;s Website on Eddie Tu, Ph.D</title>
    <link>https://gohugo-theme-ananke.pages.dev/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Eddie Tu&#39;s Website on Eddie Tu, Ph.D</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 28 Nov 2022 12:00:59 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://gohugo-theme-ananke.pages.dev/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Project RattleCam - online interactive platform</title>
      <link>https://gohugo-theme-ananke.pages.dev/post/project-7/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Nov 2022 12:00:59 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gohugo-theme-ananke.pages.dev/post/project-7/</guid>
      <description>Collaborators: Dr. Scott Boback (Dickinson College), Dr. Emily Taylor (Cal Poly), Dzung Dinh (Dickinson College)
General Project Description: Project RattleCam is a community science project created to help study and to educate the public about Prairie Rattlesnakes. Educating the public on these often maligned creatures is vital work towards the conservation of snakes, which play a crucial role in the balance of their ecosystems. The project has curated more than 60,000 photos of these snakes using remotely-deployed cameras.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project RattleCam - statisical analysis</title>
      <link>https://gohugo-theme-ananke.pages.dev/post/project-6/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Nov 2022 12:00:58 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gohugo-theme-ananke.pages.dev/post/project-6/</guid>
      <description>Collaborators: Dr. Scott Boback (Dickinson College), Dr. Emily Taylor (Cal Poly)
General Project Description: Project RattleCam is a community science project created to help study and to educate the public about Prairie Rattlesnakes. Educating the public on these often maligned creatures is vital work towards the conservation of snakes, which play a crucial role in the balance of their ecosystems. The project has curated more than 60,000 photos of these snakes using remotely-deployed cameras.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project RattleCam - Analysis of Zooniverse users</title>
      <link>https://gohugo-theme-ananke.pages.dev/post/project-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Nov 2022 11:00:59 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gohugo-theme-ananke.pages.dev/post/project-5/</guid>
      <description>Collaborators: Dr. Scott Boback (Dickinson College), Dr. Emily Taylor (Cal Poly)
General Project Description: Project RattleCam is a community science project created to help study and to educate the public about Prairie Rattlesnakes. Educating the public on these often maligned creatures is vital work towards the conservation of snakes, which play a crucial role in the balance of their ecosystems. The project has curated more than 60,000 photos of these snakes using remotely-deployed cameras.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project RattleCam - processing raw data</title>
      <link>https://gohugo-theme-ananke.pages.dev/post/project-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Nov 2022 11:00:59 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gohugo-theme-ananke.pages.dev/post/project-4/</guid>
      <description>Collaborators: Dr. Scott Boback (Dickinson College), Dr. Emily Taylor (Cal Poly)
General Project Description: Project RattleCam is a community science project created to help study and to educate the public about Prairie Rattlesnakes. Educating the public on these often maligned creatures is vital work towards the conservation of snakes, which play a crucial role in the balance of their ecosystems. The project has curated more than 60,000 photos of these snakes using remotely-deployed cameras.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PCA for Anomaly Detection</title>
      <link>https://gohugo-theme-ananke.pages.dev/post/project-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jun 2021 10:58:08 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gohugo-theme-ananke.pages.dev/post/project-3/</guid>
      <description>Collaborators: Tim Wickard
Description:
This project was done as consulting work for a manufacturing plant which had a vast amount of process data from their plant&amp;rsquo;s sensor network (data have been anonymized here). The goal was to build a model to detect anomalies in the data that could contribute to defects in the produced membranes. We used Principal Component Analysis (PCA) to find anomalous data and learn which features in the sensor network contributed the most to this anomalous behavior.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Association and other forms of positive dependence for Feller evolution systems</title>
      <link>https://gohugo-theme-ananke.pages.dev/post/project-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2021 11:00:59 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gohugo-theme-ananke.pages.dev/post/project-2/</guid>
      <description>(Paper published in &amp;ldquo;Theory of Probability and Its Applications&amp;rdquo; in January 2021)
Abstract: We characterize various forms of positive dependence for a general class of time-inhomogeneous Markov processes called Feller evolution processes (FEPs) and for jump-FEPs. General FEPs can be studied through their time and state-space dependent (extended) generators. We will use the time and state-space dependent (extended) generators and time and state-space dependent Lévy measures to characterize the positive dependence of general FEPs and jump-FEPs, respectively.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>On association and other forms of positive dependence for Feller processes</title>
      <link>https://gohugo-theme-ananke.pages.dev/post/project-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2019 10:58:08 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gohugo-theme-ananke.pages.dev/post/project-1/</guid>
      <description>(Paper published in &amp;ldquo;Journal of Applied Probability&amp;rdquo; in June 2019)
Abstract: We characterize various forms of positive dependence, such as association, positive supermodular association and dependence, and positive orthant dependence, for jump-Feller processes. Such jump processes can be studied through their state-space dependent Lévy measures. It is through these Lévy measures that we will provide our characterization. Finally, we present applications of these results to stochastically monotone Feller processes, including Lévy processes, the Ornstein–Uhlenbeck process, pseudo-Poisson processes, and subordinated Feller processes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dependence structures in Lévy-type Markov processes</title>
      <link>https://gohugo-theme-ananke.pages.dev/post/project-0/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2017 10:58:08 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gohugo-theme-ananke.pages.dev/post/project-0/</guid>
      <description>(Dissertation awarded August 2017)
Abstract: In this dissertation, we examine the positive and negative dependence of infinitely divisible distributions and Lévy-type Markov processes. Examples of infinitely divisible distributions include Poissonian distributions like compound Poisson and α-stable distributions. Examples of Lévy-type Markov processes include Lévy processes and Feller processes, which include a class of jump-diffusions, certain stochastic differential equations with Lévy noise, and subordinated Markov processes. Other examples of Lévy-type Markov processes are time-inhomogeneous Feller evolution systems (FES), which include additive processes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://gohugo-theme-ananke.pages.dev/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gohugo-theme-ananke.pages.dev/about/</guid>
      <description>I am an Assistant Professor of Mathematics and Data Analytics at Dickinson College in Carlisle, PA. I have taught courses which include lower and upper level probability and statistics, machine learning, data science seminars, and various areas of mathematics. My research areas include work in theoretical probability, applied statistics, and data science. I am also passionate about community science engagement, and my current work focuses on data analytics for the community science group &amp;ldquo;Project RattleCam&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://gohugo-theme-ananke.pages.dev/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gohugo-theme-ananke.pages.dev/contact/</guid>
      <description>Email LinkedIn GitHub ResearchGate Dickinson College</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
